Sociology 094: The Sociology of Higher Education Records UA253
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Sociology 094: The Sociology of Higher Education Records
2017
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
UA253
121.3 Megabytes
12 Digital Object(s) 12 digital objects containing 12 files.
This collection contains student classwork, including final presentations and presentation scripts, for Sociology 094: The Sociology of Higher Education.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred in 2018, accession UA-2018-059.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in one series: Fall semester 2017.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains final presentations and presentation scripts for six groups of students enrolled in SOC094 in Fall 2017.
Biographical / Historical
This course uses the Digital Collections and Archives as a laboratory for researching and writing on topics related to U.S. higher education, including admissions policies, affirmative action, intercollegiate athletics, vocational programs, and campus sexual assault. In this course, students complete group research projects based on primary sources available in the archives. In 2017, this course was taught by Freeden Blume Oeur.
- Fall semester, 2017; UA253.001; 121.3 Megabytes; 12 Digital Object(s) 12 digital objects containing 12 files.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically by project year.
  Conditions Governing Access
  This series contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains final presentations and presentation scripts for six groups of students enrolled in SOC094 in Fall 2017.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Transferred in 2018, accession UA-2018-059.
  - 1910s Campus Tour Presentation, 2017; UA253.001.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.18 Megabytes
    Open for research.
    Final project presentation.
  - 1910s Campus Tour Script, 2017; UA253.001.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); .05 Megabytes
    Final project script.
  - 1920s Campus Tour Presentation, 2017; UA253.001.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.3 Megabytes
    75 years from the date of creation.
  - 1920s Campus Tour Script, 2017; UA253.001.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); .05 Megabytes
  - 1930s Campus Tour Presentation, 2017; UA253.001.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 10.15 Megabytes
  - 1930s Campus Tour Script, 2017; UA253.001.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); .09 Megabytes
  - 1960s Campus Tour Presentation, 2017; UA253.001.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.14 Megabytes
  - 1960s Campus Tour Script, 2017; UA253.001.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); .19 Megabytes
  - 1970s Campus Tour Presentation, 2017; UA253.001.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.17 Megabytes
  - 1970s Campus Tour Script, 2017; UA253.001.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); .17 Megabytes
  - 1980s Campus Tour Presentation, 2017; UA253.001.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.92 Megabytes
  - 1980s Campus Tour Script, 2017; UA253.001.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); .11 Megabytes